--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:阳阳  字幕调校:阳阳  招募Q号:76846146
威力战士
Powertron!
联合-攻击!
Special Attack!
可恶 下次我不会放过你们的
Curses! I'll get you next time, Powertron!
BUG之王 别跑
Hold it, Kingburg!
可恶 让他跑了
Dammit! Did he get away?
不过 我们会保护 这网络世界的和平
However, we Powertrons will uphold the peace of the network!
耶!
Yeah!
跟电视里的感觉不一样
That was nothing like the stuff on TV.
看着好俗气
That was so cheap!
怎么这么贵啊
Man, that's like way too expensive.
因为是广岛演唱会那一场的现场碟
Like I said, it's from that show in Hiroshima.
就是我没去的那次?
The one I couldn't go to?
小丽被那群人闹场捣乱 唱不下去了
When Rei went fumbling her song 'coz those guys started trouble…
之后未麻顶替小丽接着唱 碟里全录了下来
And this is the MiniDisc from when Mima sang in Rei's place.
未麻唱小丽的歌 很珍贵哦
It's a precious sample of Mimarin's singing voice!
嗯 另外 那个传闻是真的吗
Oh, yeah… Is that rumor true?
哦 那个
Oh, that?
只剩三本 只剩三本
Three left, only three left…
Cham的最新报导 只剩三本
Last issue of CHAMMINGBIRD… only three left.
400元 400元
400 yen… 400 yen…
我也听说了
Yeah, I read about that too.
听说她今天就要宣布 因为这是她在这里的最后一场演唱会了
I heard she's announcing it today coz it's the last concert here.
就这么小的一场演唱会? 未麻可有点冷漠哦
At a nothing show like this? That's pretty cold of Mimarin!
最近未麻的单独活动越来越多了
There's been lots of solo activity going on lately…
她也确实挺适合当演员的
And only Mimarin's like worthy of being an actress?
看 那些人又来了
Look, they're back.
上个礼拜就是他们来捣乱
The guys that caused trouble last week.
希望今天不要又来乱搞
I just hope they don't make a mess today, of all days.
好紧张
I'm getting nervous!
不要动 不要动
Come on, sit still!
这个是怎么了 缝线都磨掉了
Hey, what's up with this!? This is all frayed!
咦?我不知道啊
Don't look at me!
-给我一些透明胶带 -喂?你好
-Get me some masking tape! -Hello? Yes.
记住你第二首歌的前奏 未麻
Remember your entrance in the second song, Mima!
别给我压力啊
Don't pressure me!
我要喝水
I need a drink!
-对不起 过会儿我给你打回去 -唱完再喝
-I'm sorry. I'll call you back. -You can have drinks after the event.
要上了
You're on!
看来她们已经准备好了
And it looks like they're set.
有请她们登场 掌声欢迎 CHAM
Without further adieu, please welcome to our stage… CHAM!!
未麻的部屋
♪ 如果爱情出了问题
♪ Got a question about your love?
♪ 擦干眼泪 稍等片刻
♪ Send a cry for help and wait a bit.
♪ 如果你发现自己心跳不已
♪ Love makes your heart race.
♪ 那意味着爱已降临
♪ If it means you're loved in the end…
♪ 要把握机会
♪ be much more aggressive…
♪ 积极面对
♪ because you will get a chance.
♪ 爱的天使终会向你微笑
♪ The angel of love smiles at you.
未麻 未麻 未麻 未麻
Mima! Mima! Mima!
未麻应该演戏而不是唱歌
Mima should be acting, not singing!
我做不到
I can't do this after all!
莉香…
Mika…
他们想让她演电视剧
They want her in a drama series.
再好不过了
There are no better deals than this!
为什么不能边唱边演?
She can act AND sing! That should be all right!
她和组合里的另外两人 日程安排已经有冲突了
Her schedule with the other two is already starting to mismatch!
她没有受过演员的训练
She didn't go through those hard lessons to become an actress!
电视制作人已经称赞过未麻的演技了
The TV producer praised Mima's acting!
可是未麻自己的感受呢?
But what about MIMA'S feelings!?
♪ …稍等片刻
♪ And wait a bit.
♪ 如果你发现自己心跳不已
♪ Love makes your heart race.
♪ 那意味着爱已降临
♪ If it means you're loved in the end…
♪ 要把握机会
♪ be much more aggressive…
♪ 积极面对
♪ because you will get a chance.
♪ 爱的天使终会向你微笑
♪ The angel of love smiles at you.
谢谢大家
Thank you very much.
这是一场开心的演唱会 但我们只剩下一首歌了
It was a fun concert, but we only have one song left…
可我们才刚来啊
We just got here!
嗯 在唱最后一首歌之前 有件事要向大家宣布
Umm… Before our last song, we have news to tell you…
嗯 在CHAM的这些年 未麻很开心…
Um, I, Mima Kirigoe, had a fun time as a member of CHAM…
一边呆着去
Out of the way!
我们干什么了?
What did we do!? HUH!?
别装了 臭打工的
Quit showin' off! You're only a part-timer!
滚一边去 混蛋
Outta my face, ya asshole!
滚出去!
YOU get out of here!
什么 你叫谁滚出去 混蛋
What the hell!? Who are you telling to leave, you fucker!?
不是我说的…
It wasn't me!
刚才扔罐子的人 给我出来
What are you doing!? Get the hell over here, whoever threw that!
滚出去! 滚出去!
Go home! Go home!
-妈的 -滚出去! 滚出去! 滚出去!
-Dammit! -Go home! Go home! Go home! Go home!
又来了
Them again!
终止演出吧
We're canceling the show!
可今天是…
But today is!
闭嘴 妈的
Shut up! Goddammit!
滚出去 滚出去 滚出去 滚出去
Go home! Go home! Go home! Go home!
停下
Stop it!
今天
Today…
本来希望能和大家 一起开心的度过
Just today… I wanted to have a good time with all of you!
有些人是什么态度
What attitude from some no-namer!
你这家伙
You little!?
你这怪胎想干嘛
What do you want, you freak?
我们走
Let's go!
其实 今天 我…
A-Actually… as of today, I…
从今天起 未麻就要离开CHAM了
As of today, Mima will graduate from CHAM!
什么? 为什么?
-What!? -Why?
谢谢大家
Thank you all.
在CHAM的两年半里 我和大家度过了美好的时光
I'm really happy that I spent the last 2 1/2 years with you all as part of CHAM!
今后 我会尽力去做好一个演员 也希望大家支持
I hope you'll support me as I do my best as a rookie actress.
这是我的最后一首歌
So this will be my last song. Please listen.
对她的经纪人来说 这么做是理所当然
Well, it totally makes sense from the agency's point of view.
做偶像歌手确实赚不到钱啊
Pop idols just don't make money… right?
人得往高处走啊
Metamorphosis, huh?
♪ 我依然记得
♪ I still remember well…
♪ 你带给我的温暖
♪ that warmth you'd given me.
♪ 在温和的阳光里
♪ It was in the gentle rays of sunlight.
♪ 我相信
♪ I had believed that…
♪ 在过去的岁月里
♪ the days past when…
♪ 我们始终相爱
♪ we were in love, were everything.
♪ 如今 回忆拥抱着我
♪ Now, embraced by the memories…
♪ 我的心却已麻木
♪ I have become a coward.
♪ 我再也无法感觉到
♪ I am choosing to live a life that…
♪ 生活中的…
♪ I can't feel any…
未麻 别离开我们 别走
-Mimarin! -Don't leave us! Don't quit!
未麻 未麻
Mimarin! Mimarin!
谢谢
Thank you.
我一直都在看未麻之部屋
I'm always looking at Mima's Room!
糟糕 乳酪坏掉了
Geez! This cheese already went bad!
真抱歉 昨天忘了喂你们
I'm sorry… I forgot to feed you yesterday.
今天发生的地震
The earthquake that happened in Mie prefecture…
摧毁了整个地区
flattened towns throughout the region.
政府报告两百人死亡 但是 总受灾人数 尚无法确定
The government reports 200 dead, but the total number of victims are…
很多人被压在瓦砾下 生死未明
yet to be determined since many more are missing amid the rubble.
当局已经派遣军队展开救援
Authorities have called in troops for rescue operations…
但由于该地区没有恢复照明…
however, because the area is already getting dark…
这几年工作辛苦了
Thanks for all the work over the years.
再见了 偶像歌手未麻
Bye bye, Mima the pop idol.
"请永远为我们唱下去"
"Sing for us forever"…
我真的做不到
I really can't do that.
我喜欢看未麻之部屋 我已经与(未麻的房间)建立了联系
"I always like looking into Mima's Room. I've put up a link to Mima's Room."
这是什么
What is this?
-喂 -未麻 你在家啊
-Hello? -Mima! You're home!
妈妈
Mom!
嗯 我很好 你呢
Yeah, I'm fine! How are you?
真的
Really?
嗯 今天是最后一次 以后我不会再唱歌了
Yeah. Today was the last one. No more singing for me.
我记得你以前一直想做歌手的啊
I remember when you kept saying you wanted to be a singer.
这是我的一个好机会 我已经跟你说过了
This is my big chance! I told you that already!
我们一直很喜欢你的歌
Lately, we've all been looking forward to each new single!
你爷爷每次都要买20张碟
Your uncle over in Yamaguchi buys 20 copies every time!
你不了解这个行业 妈妈
You just don't understand this industry, Mom.
你不是最会唱歌吗
Wasn't singing what you were best at?
偶像歌手的形象限制了我的发展
The pop idol image is suffocating me!
再说 如今偶像…
Besides, nowadays pop idols are…
等一下 有电话打进来
Wait, I've got a call on the other line…
我是未麻
Yes, Kirigoe here…
喂
Hello?
妈 是打错的
Mom? Just a wrong number.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
噢 等一下 浴室
Oh, wait! The bath!
五分钟后再打过来
Call me back in five minutes.
噢 老妈
Oh, Mother!
传真?谁发来的
A fax? Who's it from?
(叛徒 叛徒 叛徒 叛徒 叛徒 叛徒)
Traitor traitor traltor TRAiTor TrAltoR TralTor
你是谁
Who are you?
"Who are you?"
你是谁
留美 你知道那是什么意思吗
Do you know what that note means, Rumi?
这是个互联网的网址
It's an Internet home page.
噢 这个最近好像很流行
Oh, that thing that's been popular lately!
那究竟是什么呢
And what is it?
怎么说呢…
How can I describe it?
就相当于是把电脑连在一起
It's kind of like computer networks.
然后呢?
And?
比如这个人说的 "与未麻之部屋 建立了联系"
Considering that this person "put up a link to Mima's Room"…
那这个"未麻之部屋" 就应该是个网站的名字
this "Mima's Room" thing is the title of a web site.
你一点也没听懂吧?
You don't get it, do you?
嗯! 完全不懂!
Nope. Not one bit.
好了
All right!
抱歉让大家久等
Sorry to keep you waiting.
我们已经准备好了
We're ready for the take!
别逗我笑
Don't make me laugh!
明明是自己要笑
You're laughing on your own!
5秒钟
5 seconds!
4 3 2
4, 3, 2…
那个被谋杀的莉香 她的妹妹来了
The younger sister of Rika, the murder victim, is here.
你要见她吗
Would you like to see her?
山城君
Mr. Yamashiro.
你知不知道犯人为什么要剥下受害人的皮
Do you know why the culprit peels off the skin of his victims?
我想他能从中得到某种性快感?
I assume he gets sexual stimulation from such activities…
他是想要成为一个… 成为什么?
-He wants to become one. -Become… what?
一个女人 或者…
A woman… or…
卡!
CUT!
落合小姐果然是个厉害的演员
Eri Ochiai is a great actress after all!
摄影机一开 她就好像变成了另外一个人
She's a completely different person when the camera is rolling!
很好
That's good!
下一幕 第32幕
NEXT! Scene 32!
莉香的妹妹 该你了
Rika's sister, you're on!
是!
Here!
帮我拿着
Hold this!
紧张吗
Nervous?
有一点
A bit.
就只有一句台词 也没什么可紧张的啊
Not much to get nervous about when you have only one line…
我们的大明星怎么样了
How's our star actress?
田所先生 她就要开始了
Mr. Tadokoro. She's just going on now.
你是谁
"Who are you?"
你…
"Who…"
就是这么回事
That's what I mean!
早上好
Good morning!
Morning!
早上好
Good morning.
嗨 大家好
Hello, everyone.
早上好
Good morning.
涉谷老师也来啦
Mr. Shibuya! You're here too?
早上好 惠利 感觉怎么样
Hi, Eri. How's it going?
先生 你写的台词好绕口 我实在念不下去了
Sir, your lines are too hard! I don't want to do it anymore!
不要这么说
Don't say that!
但剧情太完美了 我最喜欢这种类型
But the story is really good!! I love stuff like this!
嘴真够甜的
You're good at egging people on!
惠利 这是你的影迷来信
Eri. There were this many fan letters sent to the station!
多谢
Thank you, Mr. Tejima.
小黑
Kuro…
呃 这封不是给你的
Oh, this one's not for you.
好好工作
Well, keep up the good work.
老师 告诉我
So, Sir, tell me!
凶犯到底是谁啊
Who's the criminal?
不行 不能说 说了就没意思了
Sorry, can't tell you. That'd spoil the fun.
那你到底准备把凶犯怎么样
So what ARE you going to do about the criminal?
要快点做决定了
You're gonna have to make your mind up soon.
早上好 手岛先生、涉谷老师
Good morning, Mr. Tejima! Mr. Shibuya!
噢 你好
Oh, hello there…
未麻在剧组里的评价不错
Mima's getting good reviews. Even among station staff.
既然这样 她的戏份 好像少了点吧 哈
If that's the case, don't you think she's got too few lines?
听到没? 涉谷
So he says, Shibuya.
咦 不要看我
Hey, don't look at me!
老师 多给未麻点机会嘛
Sir! Please! Make use of Mima just a little bit more!
但是她是个偶像歌手 不是吗
But see… She's a pop idol, right?
这不太好用啊
They're really hard to use…
那没关系 她已经不是偶像歌手了
That's no problem! She's done with being a pop idol!
真的?
Really?
我们要给她的形象 来个大转变
We want to give her a drastic image change, too.
我们准备好了
We're ready for the take!
对了 这个给未麻
Oh, this is for Mima.
你是谁
"Who are you?"
5秒钟
5 seconds!
4 3 2
4, 3, 2…
田所先生!
Mr. Tadokoro!?
Mr. Tadokoro!
田所先生!
Mr. Tadokoro!!
我没事
I'm all right…
这是怎么回事
What the hell is this!?
我想是那封信爆炸了
I think that letter just exploded!?
叫救护车 叫救护车
Call an ambulance! An ambulance!
是
Yes!
(这是一次警告 下一次 将是动真的)
Is a warning. The next one will be REAL.
好了
We're all set now.
留美 你真棒
Rumi, you're really amazing!
现在我帮你登陆上网
I'll sign you up for online services now.
好
Okay.
留美 你觉得怎么样
What do you think, Rumi?
什么?
About what?
那天的那件事
About that thing the other day.
哦 那个
Oh, that…
信用卡号码
Credit card number…
要不要叫警察
Shouldn't we have called the police?
田所说不用 我们也没办法
Mr. Tadokoro said not to. We can't do anything about it.
可这是犯罪啊
But it was a crime!
也许遭殃的本来应该是我
And it might have been me!
没关系 只不过是个恶作剧
It's okay. It was just a prank.
而且田所伤得不重
Fortunately, Mr. Tadokoro wasn't badly hurt.
所以未麻你也不用担心
So you shouldn't worry, Mima.
未麻 我把这解释给你听 认真听着
Anyway, Mima, I'll explain all of this so listen carefully.
好的
Okay!
这是万维网的浏览器
This is a browser for the World Wide Web.
你双击这个就会启动了
You launch it by double-clicking here.
双击是啥?
Wha? Double-clip?
不要打断我
What are you going to do with a clip?
但是
But…
看 在地址栏中 键入URL
See, next to "location" you enter the URL.
不难吧?
It's not hard, is it?
拜托 留美
Come on, Rumi!
你可以用日语跟我解释吗
Can't you explain it to me in Japanese?
真是 你啥都不懂 买个电脑来干嘛
Boy! Why did you buy a computer when you don't know anything about it?
因为他们都说很简单
Because they said it was easy!
好吧 我从头再给你讲一遍
Oh, all right. I'll explain it from the beginning once more…
嗯
Okay!
h t t p
H… T… T… P…
有东西了
Ooh, something came up!
哈 我干得挺好
Hey, I'm doing pretty well!
然后
And now…
找到了
There it is!
(未麻之部屋)
Mima's Room
(未麻的日记)
Mima's Diary
这是什么
Mima's Diary What's this?
真糟糕
"It was just terrible!"
我搞砸了舞蹈 忘记了歌词
"I screwed up the choreography, AND forgot my lyrics."
我对不起我的歌迷
"I feel so sorry to all my fans!"
今天早上 我左脚先下了火车
"This morning, when I got off the train left foot first…"
结果引来一天的倒霉事
"was when all the bad stuff started."
我一直注意上火车或者
"I always make it a point that my right foot…"
进浴室时 要先迈右脚
"goes first into the train and into the bath."
有人真的很了解我 这是什么
Someone sure knows me! What's this?
今天是我21岁生日
"Today was my 21st birthday."
雪子 小丽和其他同事给我搞了个聚会 好开心
"Yukiko, Rei, and the staff at the agency held a party for me. It was terrific!"
回家前 我去那家超市买了点东西
"Coming home, I went grocery shopping at the usual store."
我买了矿泉水和牛奶
"I got mineral water and milk."
牛奶买的是高档的母牛牌的
"The milk just has to be Cow Brand milk."
偶尔要对自己好一点
"I have to allow myself at least this much luxury."
还买了鱼食
"And food for my precious fish, of course…"
5月12日 Double Bind剧组里 落合惠利小姐的表演给我印象很深
"May 12th. I was impressed with Eri Ochiai's performance in Double Bind."
一开拍她就像是变了个人
"She's another person when the camera is rolling…"
这些都是什么
What is all this?
他们怎么会知道这么多
How do they know this much?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是心理医生浅宫瞳子
I'm Dr. Toko Asamiya, specializing in psychiatry.
是你已过世姐姐的心理医生
I was your late sister's psychiatrist.
我有些问题想问你
There are some things I'd like to ask you.
山城警探 又一个
Detective Yamashiro! Another one!
什么
What!?
这已经是第五个了
This is the fifth victim…
总共才3个镜头
Just three shots.
为这个离开CHAM值得吗
Is this work really worth leaving CHAM for?
留美 你知不知道 要得到一个
Rumi. Do you know how hard it is to get a character…
哪怕是这么小的电视剧角色有多难?
that reappears in a drama series? Even a role like this?
我知道 但是
Yes, I do. But…
未麻能否成为真正的演员 就看现在了
This is where Mima proves if she can be seen as a real actress or not.
我觉得 还是应该 继续让她当偶像歌手
But we should sell Mima as a pop idol!
留美啊 现在跟你当偶像时相比 时代已经不同了
Really. Times are different from when Rumi Hidaka was a working pop idol.
我知道
I know that.
如今 大众心中 已经没有偶像歌手的地位了
Nowadays, there are no places for pop idols to appeal to the masses.
未麻能否红下去 选择正确的发展方向很重要
This is the branch point that will decide if Mima lasts or not.
只怪我当年没一直红下去
Well, excuse me for not surviving.
拜托 留美
Please, Rumi!
没有比让未麻做演员更好的事了
There's nothing better than having Mima be able to change into an actress!
她来东京是为了唱歌的
She came to Tokyo to sing…
你想想
Think!
卖唱片其实没给我们赚到多少钱
On record sales we make practically nothing!
但我真的希望能多给她点镜头
But I do wish that they'd use her a little bit more…
没赚到钱真是对不起啊
Sorry we're not that profitable!
早上好
Good morning!
新的CHAM组合怎么样
How's the new CHAM going?
(Double Bind)
Double Bind
那电视剧好难看
It's the pits!
Double Bind? 我也看了
Double Bind… yeah, I saw it too.
真无聊
It was so boring!
为什么日本的心理悬疑片 都是一个套路
Why do all psycho-thrillers made in Japan turn out that way?
也没怎么看到未麻
Mimarin's not in it!
对啊 上周她才只有4个镜头
Oh yeah. How many scenes was she in last week? Four?
是3个
Three.
谁来帮帮未麻啊
Somebody save Mimarin! PLEASE!
(互联网主页 你也可以做一个)
A HOME PAGE ON THE INTERNET: You can make one too!
今天早上 我左脚先下了火车…
This morning, when I got off the train left foot first…
嗨 是未麻
Hey, It's Mimarin!
早上好
Good morning!
早上好 未麻
Good morning, Mimarin!
连续剧请加油啊
Break a leg with that drama series!
嘿 等等 未麻
Hey, wait, Mimarin…
变成了演员就都不友好了吗
Do they get all unfriendly when they become actresses?
(机动车肇事逃逸)
Hit-And-Run at Shinkaido.
(土居正 18岁 重伤)
Tadashi Doi (18), in critical condition.
早上好
Good morning!
早上好 未麻
Good morning, Mima.
干杯
Cheers!
怎么回事
What's going on?
CHAM的新单曲
CHAM's new single…
噢 她们排到第83位了?
Oh, wow! They got 83rd?
我们以前从没上过排行榜
We never even made the charts before.
1 2
One, two…
恭喜
Congratulations!
我们做到了
We did it!
现在更要努力工作
Now we've got to work together really hard!
唉 可是会有观众吗
But will there be anyone in the audience?
别担心啦 未麻
Sure there will be, Mima!
这是下次的剧本 台词多了一些
Your next script. It has a few more lines.
嗯
Yeah.
你们两人干得不错
You've both done great!
CHAM光有她们两人 就行了嘛
CHAM is totally okay being a duo!
嗨 请问你现在有没有经纪人
Hey, you. Are you currently in any talent agency?
对不起 我在赶时间
I'm sorry, I'm in a hurry.
喂
Hey!
想不想当模特?
Wouldn't you be interested in being a model?
模特?
Model?
卡!
Cut!
不错 准备下一幕
OK! We're going to move for the next scene!
那女孩是谁
Who's that girl?
不知道
I don't know.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey!
我看了下星期的剧本 你真棒
I saw next week's script, Shibuya. You're wonderful!
我都没想到会这么发展
I didn't think it would come to this!
说实话 我还有更好的点子
To tell the truth, I have an even more drastic idea.
太好了
Fantastic!
可是
But…
不知道未麻能不能接受
I wonder if it would be all right for Mima…
还有她的经纪人
or rather, her agency.
未麻的角色 高仓阳子
Mima's character, Yoko Takakura, changes…
在脱衣舞夜总会里被客人们强奸后 性格彻底转变
personalities completely when she's raped by the customers at a strip show.
你疯了! 强奸戏?
You're crazy! A rape scene!?
她是后半部戏的主角 这角色重要程度大增了
She's the key figure in the second half of the series! It's an important role!
但是未麻是个偶像
But Mima's a pop idol!
别担心 未麻
Don't worry, Mima.
我会叫制作人改掉
We'll ask the producer and get it changed.
喂喂 等一下
Hey, hey. Wait a minute!
现在光是剧本的延误 就已经让制作方着急了
The scripts are already behind schedule as is, and the art staff is getting antsy!
如果我们再争下去 会怎么样
How will it look if we make it worse by arguing?
而且我已经告诉涉谷 她的偶像形象改变了
I even told Shibuya that she was changing out from a pop idol!
保护艺人是我们的工作
It's our job to protect the celebrities in our agency!
未麻绝不会去做这种事情
There's no way Mima can do such a thing!
没关系 留美
It's all right, Rumi.
我会做的
I'll do it.
因为我决定了要做演员
Because I decided that I WILL become an actress.
未麻
Mima!
太棒了 未麻
I see. You're really wonderful, Mima!
这种事对演员来说没什么 朱迪福斯特不也做过嘛
This kind of thing is commonplace for actresses! Jodie whatshername did it too!
(美国影视演员)
未麻 要考虑清楚
Mima, please think it out.
你想过后果吗
Do you realize what will happen as a result of this?
没事 我又不会真的被强奸
It's not as if I'm really getting raped!
尽管 我父母看到后肯定会不高兴
Although… I'm sure my parents will flip when they see me like that.
不管怎样 我会做的 而且会尽全力
Anyway, I'll do it. I'll give it my best shot.
未麻
Mima…
我可不同意
I absolutely REFUSE to do it!
导演 布景怎么样
Well, Mr. Director? How does the set look?
我更希望能在真的夜总会里拍
I'd prefer to shoot in a real club…
但考虑到我们拍摄的内容 没人会让我们拍的
but considering what we're filming, nobody will let us shoot at their place.
妈的
Sheesh!
我全指望你了
Please, I'm counting on you.
好了好了好了
Hey, hey, hey, come on, Yada!
光确定下次开会的日期 有什么用
What are you going to do with just the DATE of the next meeting!?
这样哪算开会啊
That doesn't make for much of a meeting!
准备好了
OK here!
准备开始
We're ready to shoot!
第48幕  "经理被拽倒" 第一次
Scene 48, "The manager gets dragged down", take 1!
10秒钟
Ten seconds…
5 4 3 2
5, 4, 3, 2…
噢 很好
Mmmm! Looks good!
前偶像歌手演得不错啊
Ex-pop idols sure make a nice scene!
别这样 放开我
No! Stop! Let me go!
下来 快下来
Cut it off! Get off the stage!
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
出去! 我要叫警察了
Get out of here! I'll call the police!
你以为我会怕警察?
You think I give a shit about cops?
放手
Hands off!
不要!
Stop it!
放开我 不要
Let me go! Stop it!
救救我 不要
Help! Help me! No!
求求你 不要
Please! NO!
卡
Cut!
喂 你 注意你的位置
Hey, over there, hold your places!
好了 移动摄影机
OK! Now move the cameras!
真对不起
I'm so sorry…
哪里
Oh, no, it's all right.
好 接下来 强奸戏
OK, next up, the rape scene!
各就各位
Everyone, get ready!
开始
Take 1! Rolling!
不 不要 不
No! Stop! No! No! Stop!
求求你 不要
Please! Stop!
停!
Cut!
不行不行 动作要快一点
No, no, no! FASTER!
对不起
Sorry!
再来一次 从头开始
Once again, from the top!
好 开始
No break yet! Take 2!
求求你 不要
Please! Stop!
不 不要
No! Please! NO!
不要
Stop it! No!
求求你
Please!
未麻!
Mimarin!!
累死了
I'm so tired!
留美呢?
Hey, where's Rumi?
嗯?她替我去开了个会
Hmm? Oh, she had a meeting to go to for me…
呃 未麻
Hey, Mima…
其实…
You know…
没什么 你真的很努力
Nothing. You tried so hard…
作为奖励 我请你吃饭吧
As a reward for your efforts, I'll treat you to a delicious meal.
真幸运
Lucky me!
我回来了 鱼儿们
I'm home, fishies!
你们饿了吧
I wonder if you're hungry yet?
我当然也不想去做
Of course I didn't want to do it!
但我不能辜负那些一直帮我的人
But I couldn't trouble all the people who brought me this far!!
看 我不是告诉过你吗
See, didn't I tell you?
这就是你想要的工作?
Is that the job that what you wanted?
简直烂透了
That was the PITS!
我再也不想演那部戏了
I don't want to do that drama anymore!
那个制作人完全是个变态 把我的角色搞得一团糟
The producer is a total pervert, and my role is really screwed up!
在我的歌迷面前唱歌 才是我最喜欢的
Singing in front of my fans has GOT to be the best for me after all!
噢 那场戏啊
Oh… that scene?
如果说从没有过犹豫 那肯定是在说谎
Of course I would be lying if I said I didn't have any hesitations…
但我把它看作成为一个演员 必须跨过的障碍
but I looked at it as a hurdle I had to jump over as an actress.
听说收视率提高了
I heard the ratings went up.
一般来说 大众都是傻瓜
As always, the public at large are all idiots.
是的 我更愿意被看做是一个演员
Yes. I'd like to be recognized as an actress.
不是"前偶像歌手"?
Not as "the ex-pop idol"?
对
You got it!
幸好我只喜欢小丽 所以对我来说没什么关系
I was fine coz Rei was always the one I liked.
我敢打赌 所有未麻的歌迷现在都在哭
I'm sure all the Mimarin fans are crying right about now.
但是在CHAM的经历教会我很多 那是段难忘的经历
But CHAM did teach me a lot. It was a great experience in its own way.
对对 就是这样
Yeah, totally!
他们可能会大叫 "那不是真正的未麻! "
They're probably whining, "That's not Mimarin!"
(未麻之部屋)
Mima's Room
你的日子过得怎么样呢
What was YOUR day like?
今天 我还是有点沮丧
"Today, I was still a little depressed…"
但是 你们的邮件 让我感觉好多了
"but receiving e-mail from all of you made me feel a little better."
邮件?
E-mail?
6月24日 大家帮帮我
"June 24: Help me, everyone…"
每个人都在逼我去做 那完全是编剧的错
"Everyone is forcing me to do it! It's all the screenwriter's fault!"
(救救我 救救我 救救我 救救我)
Help! Help! Help! Help! Help! Help!
这 这是假的 我没写过这样的东西
This… This isn't true! I'm not writing any of this!
当然罗 是真正的未麻在写
Of course! The REAL Mima is writing this!
我能看穿你 你想再成为偶像歌手
I know that deep down in your heart you want to be a pop idol again.
不
No!
我不再
I'm no longer…
你不再什么?
No longer what?
哦 对 你不再是偶像歌手了
Oh, yeah, you're no longer a pop idol.
你现在是个肮脏的女人了
You're a filthy woman now.
没人会喜欢一个脏女人做偶像
Nobody likes idols with tarnished reputations!
不是的 不是的
That's not true! That's not true!
未麻
Mimarin!
你的光芒已经消褪了
You can't step back into that spotlight now…
但也好 还有我呢
But that's all right. I'M here.
从今往后 我在灯光下 你在阴影里
From now on, I'll be in the light, and you'll be in the shadows.
你在说什么
What are you saying!?
你到底是谁
Who in the world are you!?
没有人会再喜欢你了
Nobody likes you anymore.
你已经被玷污了! 脏女人!
You're tarnished! FILTHY!
别说了!
Stop! Stop it!
我没有被玷污!
I am not tarnished!
别走
Wait!
WAIT!
Love makes your heart race.
If it means you're loved in the end…
be much more aggressive…
because you will get a chance.
The angel of love smiles at you.
有人吗?
Is anyone there?
你是否看到了天使的翅膀
Can you see the angel's white wings?
也许她的眼睛正注视着你
Or her eyes gazing at you…
她甜蜜的嗓音 她温柔的双手
her sweet voice, her gentle hands?
她只为你而存在
She is here just for you.
她保护着你
She is protecting you…
就在你的身边
from somewhere nearby.
Got a question about…
Love makes your heart race.
If it means you're loved in the end…
be much more aggressive…
案发是凌晨1点左右
It happened about 1 o'clock this morning.
对了 昨晚我给你家打电话 你居然没在
Hey, I called you last night and you weren't in…
日 被你发现了… 算了 哈哈
"Oh shit! How did you know?" Yeah, right.
你看到了未麻之部屋吗?
Did you see "Mima's Room"?
嗯 那真的是她吗
Yeah, but is that really her?
谁知道
No clue.
根据那个网站 未麻今天会出场表演
According to that page, Mimarin's gonna be on stage today.
怎么可能
No way!
(警方表示 死者涉谷贵雄 被利器刺中十几刀)
Police say Shibuya was stabbed umpteen times with a sharp object…
(著名编剧遭残杀 死者 涉谷贵雄 34岁)
Popular Script Writer SLAUGHTERED! The victim: Takao Shibuya (34)…
这事很可怕 但我们担心也没用
It sure is a shocking incident, but us worrying about it won't help.
我们得把精力 放到别的事情上去
We have to put our minds on something else.
但是还有炸弹信那件事
But there was that letter bomb too…
喂喂 你认为涉谷的谋杀 与那事有关?
You think Mr. Shibuya's murder is connected with that?
我没那么说
I didn't say that…
你电视剧看得太多了 别担心
You watch too many TV tabloid shows. Don't worry about it.
那表情可不像个明星 笑一笑
You won't become a star looking like that! Smile!
(涉谷在1990年获得新作家奖 然后…)
Shibuya won the New Writers' Prize in 1990, and then…
你.
Serves…
对吧
right!?
怎么了 未麻 未麻
What's wrong? Mima! MIMA!
未麻会没事吗
But will Mima be all right?
怎么了
Why?
听说那个摄影师专门剥人衣服
That photographer specializes in getting people to strip!
那又怎么样
So what?
她已经习惯了
She's got that part down pat!
我肯定她会在摄影师面前全脱哦
I'm sure she's totally showing it off in front of the photographer!
全脱…
Like, TOTALLY!
该你们上场了 快点
Isn't it time you were on? Hurry up.
是
Yes'm.
唔 我喜欢这个表情
Oooh… I like that expression.
用手拨拨头发
Try running your fingers through your hair.
噢噢 我喜欢这样
Oh, I like this.
太好了
It's great!
♪ 香水并非为我而洒 香气却迎面而来
♪ Perfume isn't for me. And when I caught the scent…
对 就是这样 嘴唇微微张开
Yeah, just like that. Part your lips a little…
好极了 把上衣脱下来
Great. Now let's take the top off too…
♪ 我宁愿穿着舒适的牛仔
♪ I'd rather wear jeans…
♪ 而不是紧绷的西装
♪ than tight business suits.
♪ 今年 我不会强迫自己 我要穿得休闲
♪ This year, I'll not exert myself and dress casually.
♪ 我曾想做一个 配得上你的女人
♪ I wanted to be a woman that suited you…
♪ 但我知道 即使我愿意 踮起脚尖走路
♪ but I knew we would drift apart even if…
♪ 我们也终会渐行渐远
♪ I kept standing on my tippy-toes.
我想你早就下定了决心
I thought you decided to go through with this!
大家都在等你呢
Everyone is waiting for you!
来吧 未麻
Come on, Mima!
我不是告诉过你吗
See? Didn't I tell you?
你最好还是当偶像歌手
You were better off as a pop idol.
喂 未麻 你在听吗
Hey Mima, are you listening?
住嘴! 你到底是谁?
Stop all this nonsense! Who are you!?
我?我是个偶像歌手
Me? I'm a pop idol.
大家都在等着我
Everyone's waiting for me.
所以我现在要和小丽和雪子一起演唱了
So I'm going to sing with Rei and Yukiko again.
不 不对
No, I'm not!
我是一个演员
I'm an actress!
别傻了
Don't be silly!
没人希望你做那种事
No one really wants that!
等等
Wait!
大家希望的是…
What everyone wants is…
♪ …拿起漫画书 丢掉晦涩的大部头
♪ from comics than difficult books and…
♪ 我只想走我自己的路
♪ I want to stay the way I am forever.
♪ 伴着微风而行
♪ Walking past, making a breeze…
♪ 尽赏良辰美景
♪ burning the scenery into my memories.
♪ 不再在意没有人陪伴
♪ I am fine even if I'm alone.
♪ 因为这孤独只属于我自己
♪ I have finally found a luxurious loneliness.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone!
(6月27日  多谢今天的捧场)
June 27th: Thank you for coming to the event today!
(在你们面前唱歌 是我最快乐的事)
It really is the best feeling to sing in front of all of you!
混蛋
BASTARDS!!
(脱衣女星 雾越未麻 离开偶像宝座)
Mima Kirigoe Leaving the Throne of a Pop Idol!!
嗯?
Huh?
喂
Hey!
你干吗
What are you doing?
(致"未麻狂人"先生: 谢谢你每天的信)
To Mr. ME-MANIA: Thank you for your e-mail every day…
你相信我 对吗
You believe me, right?
那不是我 是一个冒牌货
That's not me. She's an impostor!
(当然 我知道未麻永远不会做那种事)
Of course. Mimarin would never do such a thing.
(我会保护你 真正的未麻)
I will protect you, the real Mimarin.
我相信你 未麻狂人先生
I trust you, Mr. ME-MANIA.
我不会改变的
I won't change one bit.
我会永远和你在一起
I'll always be with you.
但是那个冒牌货 一直在妨碍我
But that impostor keeps getting in my way.
我该怎么办
What should I do?
(我会搞定她)
I'll get rid of her.
谢谢你 未麻狂人先生
Thank you, Mr. Me-mania!
你是我唯一的依靠
You're the only one I can depend on.
我已经不知道我自己是谁了
I don't know anything about myself anymore!
那个
Well…
是什么让你能够确定
How do you think you know that person you were…
一秒钟前的你 和现在的你是同一个人?
a second ago is the same person you are now?
答案 记忆的连续性
A continuous stream of memories.
也因为这个 我们才得以带起假面生活
Given only that, we all create illusions within ourselves…
假装心中没有另一个 受压制的自我
saying that we each have only one fixed persona.
医生 我很担心
Doctor, I'm scared…
另外一个我会做出一些 我不知道的事情
that my other self will do something that I don't know about…
没事 幻想是不会成为现实的
It's all right. There is no way illusions can come to life.
卡!
CUT!
未麻 怎么了
Mima, what's wrong?
对不起
I'm sorry!
唉 这雨真凉
Oh, man! This rain sucks!
我恐怕要感冒了
I think I'm going to catch a cold!
对不起
I'm sorry!
遮起来 遮起来
Wrap it up! Wrap it up!!
风雨虽然猛烈 但你的心却充满阳光
It's pouring really badly outside, but your heart is always, like, sunny!
那么 我们现在开始吧
Well, I think we're ready today!
"Yukiko公司"
and Yukiko's…
"CHAM之家"
"Idol Chamland"!
田所先生
Mr. Tadokoro?
他们应该已经开始播音了
I'm sure they're on the air now.
好久都没见面 你可能也想见见她们
I thought you'd like to see them coz it's been a while.
这周日下午两点 我们在茨城有个演出
We have a show this Sunday. It's at Ibaragi Sim City at 2pm.
-好久不见 -(欢迎歌迷们来捧场)
-How have you been? -People from all over, come see us!
-早就想过来看看 -(我们会等着你哦)
-Just thought I'd drop by. -We'll be waiting for you!
CHAM之家 下周同一时间 再会
Chamland will be back next week at the same time. Until then…
1 2
Two, three…
Bye Bye!
Bye bye!
很好 各位
Good show, guys.
咦 是未麻
Hey, it's Mima.
未麻!
Mima!
别走
Wait!
你是谁
Who are you!?
我告诉过你 我是真未麻
I told you! I'M the real Mima.
下一则新闻
In other news…
今日 经济企划厅针对国民生活水平
Today, the Economic Planning Agency announced a "New Citizen's Life Index"…
发布了一项"新市民生活指数"
that indicates the overall Japanese standard of living and…
好像好久不见了
It feels like I haven't seen you in a long time.
我也很忙
Well, I've been busy too.
习惯了当演员吗?
So, are you getting used to acting?
嗯
Yeah.
虽然很辛苦 但 是我自己的选择
It's hard, but I chose to do it.
你成熟了不少 未麻
You've matured quite a bit, Mima!
好在 人们似乎也很喜欢新未麻
But it's good that people seem to like the new Mima.
嗯
Yeah…
你不同意吗
That doesn't look like a face that's agreeing.
那个 未麻 有人一直在骚扰你吗
You know… Mima… Has someone been harassing you?
我一直上那个网站
I've been visiting that home page.
虽然只是抱怨你形象的改变 我觉得还是过分了点
It's a bit much, even if it's a complaint about how you changed your image…
你不看会感觉好些的
It's better if you didn't look at it.
嗯
Yeah…
但是她可能才更像真正的未麻
But maybe she is more like me than myself.
未麻?
Mima?
我深埋在心底的另一个我
My other self that I buried deep within my heart.
如果…
What if…
另一个自我自动起作用了 该怎么办
What if that other personality suddenly started acting on its own?
没事 幻想是不会成为现实的
It's all right. There is no way illusions can come to life.
停
CUT!
未麻 你在说什么
Mima! What are you saying?
唉 这句台词我已经念得快吐了
I feel like I'm gonna have nightmares about this line!
对不起
I'm sorry!
怎么了?
What's wrong?
嗯 没什么
Uh, nothing…
再来一次 从头开始
Once more, from the top…
好 开始
All right, Take 2!
下一则新闻
In other news…
今日 经济企划厅针对国民生活水平
Today, the Economic Planning Agency announced a "New Citizen's Life Index"…
发布了一项"新市民生活指数"
that indicates the overall Japanese standard of living and…
好久不见了 留美
It's been a while, Rumi.
啥?我昨天不是刚来过?
What? I was here yesterday, too!
昨天…是真的吗
Yesterday? Was that real?
你看起来怪怪的 未麻
You're weird, Mima.
未麻 你怎么了
Mima! What's wrong with you!?
你在流血
You're bleeding!
这血是真的吗
This blood is real, isn't it?
未麻
Mima!
(今天我去了原宿购物 我对购物最没抵抗力了)
Today I went shopping in Harajuku. I'm a sucker for sale items.
原来 我今天去了原宿
I guess… I went to Harajuku today…
你的意思是
You mean…
那个凶手只是她的幻觉
the murderer is an illusion she created?
是的
Yes.
她害怕一个并不存在的保安
She fears an imaginary security guard…
并且把他想象成了那件 模特连环谋杀案的凶犯
and then doubles that figure with the serial murderer of top models.
但不存在的幻象是不会杀人的啊
But illusions don't kill.
可是 如果她把她的幻想 投射到了真实的人身上
But… what if that illusion found someone to possess?
投射?
Possess??
这么说 那些被杀的男人…
Then… all those men who got murdered?
同时也都是 已经对她没用了的人
Were those who were no longer of any use to her.
山城君 请快点找到她
Find her quickly, Mr. Yamashiro.
赶在下一个牺牲者出现前
Before another victim falls prey.
多少钱
How much?
你这送披萨的真够怪的
You sure are a weird pizza man.
停下 求你了
Stop! Please stop!
唔 好极了 再来 再惹火一点
Yeah, that looks good… Come on, be more daring! More passionate!
好! 第三次!
All right! Take three!
-喂 -未麻?
-Hello? -Mima?
你那里没事吧
Are you all right over there?
你还没听说村野先生的事吗
You haven't heard yet… about Mr. Murano?
难道…
Can't be!
警方表示村野死于多处刺伤
Police say that Murano died of multiple stab wounds…
村野先生他真的…
Mr. Murano!? Really!?
我们这里已经乱成一团了
We're going crazy here!
你不要动 等我过去 听到了?
Anyway, stay put until I get there. All right!?
据了解 此次谋杀所用的凶器 极为类似于…
The weapon used in the latest murder is said to closely resemble…
上周知名编剧被杀一案 的涉案凶器
the one used in last week's killing of a popular screenwriter.
警方认为不排除仇杀可能
Police are considering a personal grudge as the motive…
并表示正努力寻找 两起案件之间可能的关联
and are looking into connections between the two cases.
雾越小姐 您能否谈谈您对 摄影师村野谋杀案的看法?
Miss Kirigoe! Please, can we get your opinion about the murder of Mr. Murano?
你知道些什么吗
Do you know anything?
这起事件与编剧涉谷的谋杀案 有什么关联?
Isn't there a connection with the killing of Mr. Shibuya the screenwriter?
雾越小姐 您能否谈谈…
Miss Kirigoe! There are rumors of a love triangle…
有关您 涉谷先生和村野先生之间 三角恋爱的传闻…
between you, Mr. Shibuya, and Mr. Murano and we…
你认为她被诅咒了?
You think she's jinxed?
有一有二就有三嘛
What happens twice happens thrice.
我们赌赌下一个会是谁吧
Let's take bets on who's next.
不要说了
Cut it out!
别理他们
Don't mind them.
我…还活着吗
Am I alive?
也许那辆卡车撞到了我 也许这一切只是一场梦
Maybe that truck hit me… and this is all a dream…
各就各位
Everyone ready?
好了未麻
OK. Mima!
比彩排时呼吸重一点
Breathe harder than during rehearsal.
你刚刚杀了人
You've just killed someone.
是
Yes.
预备 开始
And… action!
清醒了吗
Are you awake?
你是?
You are?
能告诉我你的名字吗
Can you tell me your name?
我 我叫雾越未麻
Me? I'm Mima Kirigoe.
好的 你的工作是?
Okay. And what do you do?
我是一个流行乐偶像… 不 是个演员
I'm a pop idol… no, an actress.
一定很辛苦吧
That must be hard work.
虽然很辛苦 但 是我自己的选择
It's hard, but it's what I chose to do.
她以为自己是个叫雾越未麻的年轻演员
She thinks she's a new young actress named Mima Kirigoe.
分离性身份障碍
Dissociative Identity Disorder.
简单的说 多重人格
In other words, "multiple personality syndrome."
所有的案件都是她在 变成另一人格时犯下的
All those crimes took place when she was some other persona.
那么 阳子本来的人格到哪里去了
So where's the persona of the original Yoko?
原始的人格高仓阳子
Yoko Takakura, the original persona…
对她来说成了一部剧中的人物
is nothing more than a character in a drama for her.
她本人曾是个普通的女孩 曾在脱衣舞夜总会里被强奸
Being a "normal" girl… how she was raped in a strip club…
她把这些事 全都当作是剧中的情节
Everything happened as part of her drama series.
以此来得到解脱
By doing so, she salvaged her heart.
是的 我是一个演员
That's right. I'm an actress.
卡!
Cut!
能告诉我你的名字吗
Can you tell me your name?
我 我叫高仓莉香
Me? I'm Rika Takakura.
原始的人格 高仓阳子 已经不存在了
The original persona, Yoko Takakura, no longer exists.
她杀死当模特的姐姐后 自己变成姐姐 以此来得到解脱
By killing, and later becoming, her sister the top-model, she salvaged her heart.
是的 我是一个模特
That's right. I'm a model.
好 成了
All right! That's the take!
太好了! 未麻
We did it, Mima!
未麻 干得好
Mima… Good work!
你真的很努力
I can tell you tried so hard!
留美…
Rumi…
我宣布 Double Bind 至此全部拍摄完毕
As of this moment, Double Bind is in the can!
大家幸苦了
Everyone, great job!
未麻真的太棒了 你说是不是啊 导演
You were fantastic, Mima! What do you think, Director?
她确实很出色
She really was excellent.
谢谢你们
Thanks a lot.
那么 庆功宴上见
See you at the wrap-up party.
还请多指教
We'll be talking to you.
那么 我们也走吧
Then… shall we go as well?
未麻 去换衣服
Mima, go get changed.
瞳子医生…
Dr. Touko…
哈 我已经不是瞳子了 你忘了?
Hey now! I'm not Touko anymore! Did you forget?
"幻想是不会成为现实的"
"There is no way illusions can come to life."
赶快从梦中醒来吧
You should stop dreaming soon.
惠利小姐?
Eri?
未麻怎么去了这么久
What's taking Mima so long?
我先回事务所 你送未麻回家吧
I'm going back to the office. Take Mima home, will ya?
田所先生 你刚才提到 未麻的下一份工作是?
Mr. Tadokoro. You were saying something about Mima's next job?
噢 挺不错的
Oh, it's great!
是一部电影的女主角
A starring role in a video movie.
这次要下更大的决心才行 不过这也是没办法的嘛
There are a few sketchy scenes… but what can you do?
救救我
Somebody help me!
没有人会听到的
Like anyone can hear YOUR voice right now!
你是谁?
Who are you!?
为什么要这样?
Why are you doing this!?
我是在保护我的宝贝未麻
I'm protecting my dear Mimarin!
我…我就是未麻啊
But-But I'm Mima!
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, NO!
你都不知道我就是"未麻狂人"
You didn't know I was Me-mania!
你只是装成未麻的样子
You're just PRETENDING to be Mimarin!
住手 不要 不要
STOP!
不 不要
NO! STOP!
你用这张小嘴 勾引了那位编剧和摄影师
Did you fool that screenwriter and that photographer with this little mouth?
你玷污了未麻的名字!
You tarnished Mimarin's name!
难道…是你?
Can it be… that you…
真正的未麻每天都发邮件给我
The real Mimarin e-mails me every day!
她说你一直都在妨碍她
And she says that you keep getting in her way!
是你杀了他们?
You killed them!?
你也就快死了
And you'll die soon, too!
坏女人
Bad girl!
你要按照剧本演才对
You have to follow the script!
现在 开始
And now… TAKE 2!
好 很不错
All right! Looks good!!
你是最棒的 未麻
You're the best, Mima!
未麻
Mima!
你怎么成这样了
What's wrong? You're in shambles!
我到处找你
I was looking all over for you!
留美…
Rumi…
到底发生了什么事
What in the world happened?
不可能
This can't be!!
你确定不是做梦?
Are you sure you weren't dreaming?
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
我带你回 未麻之部屋
I'm taking you back… to Mima's room.
留美 你在吗
Rumi, are you here?
什么事
What?
噢 没事
Oh, nothing…
对了 得给田所先生打个电话
Oh, that's right, I have to call Mr. Tadokoro.
不 这不是我的房间
No… This isn't my room…
当然不是 因为这里是未麻之部屋嘛
Of course not! This is Mima's room!
你是
You're!
看 我的新衣服
Look! It's the new costume!
明天演出要穿
I'm wearing it at tomorrow's show!
好看吧?很合身呢
Isn't it great? It's perfect on me!
留美?为什么?
Rumi? Why?
留美?
Rumi?
留美…
Rumi…
留美已经回家了
Oh! Rumi went home.
她说最近工作太累 要补一补觉
She said she's been busy lately and was deprived of sleep.
请别说这些奇怪的话了!
Don't say weird stuff like that!
这是个玩笑 对不对 留美
This is a joke, isn't it, Rumi!?
如果你发现自己心跳不已
Love makes your heart race.
那意味着爱已降临
If it means you're loved in the end…
怎样?唱得好吧?
What do you think? Perfect, huh?
偶像歌手还是得唱歌才行
A pop idol HAS to sing, after all!
但是
But…
你却总是在妨碍我
You just had to keep getting in my way.
留美她也很生气哦
Rumi was totally furious, too.
求求你 别这样了
Please… stop all of this!
但偶像总有歌迷保护
But a pop idol is always protected by her fans!
不管未麻向他们要求什么 他们都会答应!
They listen to any favor I, Mima, ask them!
虽然未麻狂人先生没有做到
Although Mr. Me-mania failed a wee bit…
未麻狂人 你是怎么知道他的
Me-mania? How do you know him!?
但是他们说 "种瓜得瓜 种豆得豆" 对你来说 更是如此
But, oh, well…" you reap what you sow," especially about YOU.
救命 来人救救我
Help! Somebody help me!
留美 是你吗
Please! Rumi, it's you, isn't it!?
快醒醒啊!
PLEASE WAKE UP!
该醒醒的是你
YOU'RE the one who needs to wake up!
救命 救救我
Help, help, somebody!
救命 快救救我
Help! SOMEBODY HELP ME!
救救我 快来人救救我
SOMEBODY! SOMEBODY HELP ME!!
救命 快救救我啊
HELP! SOMEBODY HELP ME!
结束吧
Let's end all of this.
我们不需要有两个未麻
We don't need two Mimas!
我才是未麻
I AM MIMA!
别开玩笑了 未麻是偶像歌手
That's funny! Mima is a pop idol!
你只是个肮脏的假货
You're just a dirty old impostor!
我才不管 我就是我
LIKE I CARE! I AM WHO I AM!!
噢 天啊
Oh, shit!
快叫警察 不 叫救护车
Get the police! No, call an ambulance!
知道
I know!
谢谢你每次送的花
Thank you for the flowers you always bring.
我会把它们摆在房间里
I'll put them in my room.
很美 很漂亮
They're pretty. Very pretty…
你来了啊 最近应该很忙吧
I didn't know you were visiting. You must be very busy lately.
啊 哪里
Oh, no.
她偶尔会变回留美 可是…
Once in a while, she returns to her Rumi persona, but…
我知道我不会再见到她了
I know I'll never see HER ever again.
但是 也多亏了她 我才能成为今天的自己
But, thanks to her, I am who I am today.
骗人的吧 雾越未麻怎么会来这地方
You're lying! There's no way Mima Kirigoe would be HERE of all places!
可能只是个长得像她的人吧
I guess she was just a look-alike.
我可是真的哦
No, I'm real!
♪ Each time I pass this station on the train…
♪ my heart fills with nostalgia.
♪ The days when I ran around town, hiding all of my feelings…
♪ in my school uniform.
♪ Take me to the first time I was in love…
♪ those four seasons when I was frantic yet doubtful.
♪ Remember all those times when just being near each other…
♪ kept our love for each other growing?
♪ I cut my hair after graduation.
♪ I wonder if you are still the same.
♪ Are you still pursuing that dream that you kept telling me about…
♪ on the way home?
♪ Take me to when my tears overflowed…
♪ to those four seasons that I felt from the bottom of my heart.
♪ Remember how in the sunsets after school…
♪ we just wanted time to spend alone?
♪ Even in this new season, I can't shake…
♪ the habit of bluffing when I am sad.
♪ I'm sure that you knew.
♪ I still remember your eyes when you looked at me silently.